"Hearts of Iron" is a
World War II simulator
It was a terrible time...
People dying
having their rights removed
and here in Sweden you were only
allowed to buy one kilo of coffee
But I'm not gonna sit here and
argue who had it the worst...
... It's pretty obvious
But the point is:
"During WWII, stay away from Europe"
So today i'm going to show you how
to win the war as New Zealand
(music playing)
Step one is to declare independence
from the U.K
We will of course face
some resistance...
... or they don't even
notice we left..
ASSHOLES !!!
But that's it... we're done.
Time to relax 9 years and
watch the fireworks
(...)
1941, Hitler has taken
a bunch of stuff
and Sweden became fascist
Just like in real life.
The germans should invade the Soviet Union
any day now !
and it's all downhill from there
But they aren't
Because...
ah ! They are too busy
invading England
oh... oh no
Of course, without the help
from New Zealand
the British Isles are
virtually defenseless
This is worrisome...
Also not my job!
That's a Soviet Yankee problem
Ooh..
Okay then...
As always, it ends with
America saving us all
United States didn't even put up a fight !!!
It's over... the allies have
been wiped out
No, not all of them...
There is one left...
...and I guess it's up to
New Zealand to stop..
Wait, unless...
... "Join Faction"...
... "Will not accept"
Okay.
New-Zealand has to stop Hitler!
At the start of the real war
The Brits took over
small Iceland
to defend it
I have to do the same with
"Small Australia"
or should i say "New New Zealand"
But even with millions of Aussies
to send to the front lines
we are still weak...
so, while the Wehrmacht are busy with
an inconvenient way of getting tacos
I shall militarize
Biggest problem we need manpower
hmmmm !
Manpower !
That's the problem... "MAN"
We need to start drafting
sheep
New Zealand has a ridiculous
amount of sheep
and from now on, every sheep
over the age of 2 has to serve
in the army
Yeaaah ! 70 million!
You see ? This is why you don't tell
everyone to come to Brazil
our 2nd problem...
We are FUCKING broke
can't afford "Hay"
We need to start making some
serious kiwi euros
Or the lambs will riot
hmm, I know of one way
but it's controversial
I'm gonna tax Dwarves
We almost went through an entire
New Zealand video
without referencing
Lord of The Rings
That was never gonna happen
I want to smash the Axis now !
Sadly... I can't do it alone
I need one of them to
switch sides
It's gonna be hard...
The absolute loyalty of...
... *exhales* at least let me
finish the sentence
Italy will fight Nazis and i shall
take on the weebs...
I have defeated Japan
Samurais could never beat
rugby players.
How did Mussolini do ?
Huh...
Better than expected
Now Germany is alone vs
seventeen nation..
What's this ?
Elections ?
oh noes...
if the fascist party wins
it's all over
dammit, once again democracy
ruins everything
but please don't take
away my democracy
the results are in *exhales*
... and the winner is
"Cupcake"
I made sheep citizens
didn't I ?
but when i was busy
with the elections
all of my allies fell...
It's only Germany
and us left
I...
I can't beat them alone
*exhales*
This wouldn't have happened
if America hadn't surrendered
No ! I said United States
has surrendered
not America...
could that mean...
nooo waaaay !!!
YES ! "Hitler" never conquered
"Delaware"
The New Zealands of America!
"Hitler"... It's on bruh !
(music...)
War is over
"World peace"
not everything is back
to normal though
"Sweden" is still fascist
and for some reason
"Estonia"... kinda rules "Brazil"
New Zealand refuses to give
Australia its independence
citing: "It belongs to New Zealand"
"because that's what the continent
is called now"
and finally... United States
is no more.
and has been replaced by the
DELAWAREANE EMPIRE
like it should be.
(His outro music)